founderscard.com 2019-03-11

# FoundersCard

## FOUNDERSCARD PRIVACY POLICY

Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your membership experience as enjoyable and rewarding as possible and we want you to use our site and membership opportunities with complete confidence. FoundersCard has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how FoundersCard collects information from its users and members of FoundersCard membership services (the "Services"), how we use the information we collect and the choices you have concerning the collection and use of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.   

### Collection and Use of Information.

Members are asked to provide certain information when they apply for membership such as name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number). The personal information collected from members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as billing and collections).

To better understand its members, FoundersCard may collect consumer, demographics and other publicly available information from third-parties. FoundersCard may use this data to provide product and service offers. We may use data in aggregate to negotiate additional benefits, or develop products and offers and to better serve our members.

FoundersCard collects information from members who use the various parts of our Services. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services.   

FoundersCard may share identifying information (like Name and address) with affiliates or business partners for their use in delivering product and service offers to members. Affiliates or business partners are not allowed to use FoundersCard data for any other purpose other than FoundersCard approved programs designed to better serve members.   

In instances where FoundersCard and a partner jointly promote the Services, FoundersCard may provide the affiliate certain personal information, as a result of the joint promotion. In this instance, the information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. FoundersCard may also generate aggregate profiles from information provided during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of members). We may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services.   

We may use registration information to contact you in a variety of ways. We may send you offers through email, phone or regular mail of FoundersCard products and services or offers on behalf of selected affiliates.   

Personal information that we collect about you includes but is not limited to your full name, email addresses, phone numbers, birthdate, credit card information, billing address, shipping address, LinkedIn link, Twitter handle, profile picture, and professional information including the name of your company and your professional title. Other personal information may be collected during the process of redeeming partner benefits, including but not limited to frequent flyer numbers, account usernames, membership IDs, and additional/alternate methods of contact including phone numbers, email addresses, etc. 

We use your personal information to verify your age (FoundersCard members must be 21 years or older), to verify your identity, to review your acceptance into FoundersCard Membership, as a necessary requirement for redeeming some benefits with our benefit partners, for billing purposes such as charging your membership fees, when we need to communicate directly with you, and for sending you marketing offers, newsletters, and other updates. 

FoundersCard adheres to the terms of the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR). Data is stored for as long as you are a prospective, current, or past member. You have the right to request a download of the personal data that is stored by FoundersCard. You have the right to request that incorrect data be updated. You have the right to request that your personal data be deleted. You have the right to withdraw consent of further processing of your data. You have the right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection supervisory authority. Your personal data is required to become a FoundersCard Member and to offer you appropriate services and benefit redemptions. We may perform automatic processing of your data to personalize your experience and communicate more effectively with you. 

We may share your personal information with benefit partners as a requirement for processing your redemptions, payment processors to charge you correctly, and marketing partners to send you offers and updates (you can unsubscribe from these emails at any time). 

### Online Advertisements

FoundersCard may share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and members collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with select advertisers. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.   

### Voluntary Surveys

We may periodically conduct both business and individual surveys. We encourage members to participate in these voluntary surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third-party.   

We take the information we receive from individuals responding to our surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other members to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third-party partners.   

### Special Cases

It is FoundersCard's policy not to use or share the personal information in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, FoundersCard may disclose personal information or information regarding use of the Services if, for any reason, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, regulations or other legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect FoundersCard, our Services, our employees or our members.   

### "Cookies" and How Founders Card May Use Them 

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. FoundersCard may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to operate and improve the products and services we provide and to manage our network and property. If you have created your own Personal Start Page, we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non-FoundersCard websites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.   

### Public Forums

Any information that you disclose in public areas of our websites or the Internet may become public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.   

### FoundersCard's Commitment to Data Security

FoundersCard has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. We will never sell your information to a third party.   

### How to Access or Modify Your Account Information

FoundersCard offers members the opportunity to access or modify information provided during registration.   

### Questions About FoundersCard's Privacy Policy

Questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein should be directed to us at [contact@founderscard.com](mailto:contact@founderscard.com).

If you have any additional questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact:

Customer Service: FoundersCard 2028 East Ben White Boulevard, Austin, TX 78741.   

### Revisions to This Policy

FoundersCard reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on our website: [https://founderscard.com](https://founderscard.com/).
